(Dr Hofstadter:)Uh, sure,
he's terrific.
Uh, Beverly, would you like
to see the math I worked out
(Sheldon:)to support our hypothesis?
Uh, you mean,
my hypothesis.
(Leonard:)I hypothesized it
all by myself.
(Dr Hofstadter:)Calm down, dear.
(Dr Hofstadter:)Mary, I'm curious.
(Dr Hofstadter:)When did you
first realize
(Dr Hofstadter:)that your son had such
a remarkable mind?
(Sheldon:)Ooh, good question.
(Sheldon:)Everyone loves stories about
Sheldon Cooper, boy genius.
(Mrs Cooper:)Well, I would have to say
when he was 13
(Mrs Cooper:)and tried to build a nuclear
reactor in the tool shed.
(Sheldon:)Ooh, this is a good one.
(Mrs Cooper:)Now, the first thing you have
to know about Shelly is
(Mrs Cooper:)ever since he was a little boy,
(Mrs Cooper:)he was always concerned
with the well-being of others.
(Mrs Cooper:)And he didn't think
that it was fair
(Mrs Cooper:)for people to pay
for electricity,
(Mrs Cooper:)so he was gonna power
the entire town for free.
(stammers)
Tell her about the uranium!
(Sheldon:)Tell her about
the uranium.
Oh, well!
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, this is adorable.
(Mrs Cooper:)When he arranged to get
some yellowcake from Chad,
(Mrs Cooper:)I thought he was talking
about Twinkies